你还要把我关在这里多久
How longer you get to keep me here
直到我能证明是你杀了他
Until I can prove that you killed him
我没有杀他
I didn't kill him
枪响时你在房子里
You were at the house when the gun went off
我本来打算去接他的
I was scheduled to pick him up
我们约好了
We had an appointment
但交通摄像头拍到你提前一小时到了
Yet traffic cameras have you there an hour early
告诉我妮可还让你做了什么
Tell me what else Nicole had you do for her
你觉得我对他有什么用？
What use do you think I had for him
也许你就是那一类...
Maybe you're the type...
哪一类？
What type is that？
爱情用完即弃
Love is a disposable
这是一个陈述句还是一个问题？
Is that a statement or a question
小心点
Careful
好了 休息一下吧
Okay let's take a break
告诉我你为她做了什么
Tell me what you did for her
说啊
Tell me
好吧
Okay
有时候
Sometimes
我会偷窥她
I watch her
为何？
why
她喜欢有观众
She liked an audience
她的故事有一点不同
Her story plays out a little differently
她说她让你停下来
She said she asked you to stop
安静点 我们一条心
Quiet,one thing we had
这就是你那天早早到那里的原因吗？
Is that why you were there early that day
你想偷窥她
You were hoping to watch her
不是
No
米克在更换他的保险箱
Mick was switching his safety deposit box he had
他在银行有个职位
an appointment at the bank
他担心安全问题
He was worried about security
我们交换钥匙时总是由我来做安全工作
I always do security when...when we switched the key
所以你知道他身上有钥匙
So you knew he had the key on him
抱歉
Sorry
老习惯
Old habit
这把枪是我父亲的
This gun belong to my father
我带着它是为了好运
I carry it for good luck
你喜欢枪 对吗？
You like guns right
我在你的档案中看到了
I read that in your profile
三八式手枪
To vintage thirty eight
别担心
Don't worry
它没有装上子弹
It's not loaded
你知道这个案子最大的问题是我不能确定
You know my biggest problem with this case is I can't decide
你有
Which motives
什么样的动机
to assign you
什么
What
好吧
Well
你对她爱入膏肓 嫉妒令你发狂
You were loved sick and jealous cuckold
渴求着花园里的鲜牛肉
Or just a garden bright beef
在任何剧本里
In either case
你都是个悲剧角色
You're a tragic character
你应该明白
I think you know that
你明白我是怎么...
You know how I
知道这一点的
Know that
因为你最好的赌注
Because your best bet
永远都是站起来
Is always gonna be to stand up
随之逃离
And walk away
在你变为真金之前
Before you get golden up
但你不会
But you won't
偷窥妮可感觉怎么样？亚伦
What did you think about un watched nicole Aaron
你肯定明白了什么
You must have thought about something
那样的女人
A woman like that
你一生只见一次
You only see once in a lifetime
你的肉棒在衣柜里是这样硬起来的吗
Did your cock throw up like this in the closet
也许你想除掉他
Maybe you could make to get him out of the way
所以那时只是为了钱
So it was just for the money then
为什么你的肉棒这么硬？
Why is your dick so hard
看起来就像
Seems like
你的余生难以抉择
the rest of your life hangs in the balance
然而
And yet
想让我继续吗
You want me to keep going
想
Yes
好舒服
Yeah
这是你想要的吗
Is this what you wanted
想要我这样吗？
想
yes
套弄你的肉棒
Throw your cock
想
Yes yes
你明白这将会是你的堕落
This is always gonna be your downfall you know
操
Fuck
这是一个小道具
Here's the little prop
舒服的肉棒
Oh fucking dick
你会习以为常
Often you get used to this
所有这一切
All of this
如此可悲
You're fucking pathetic
脆弱的盔甲
This is your armor huh
涂上纹身就觉得自己成为硬汉了吗？
Like you feel like a tough guy when you need a tattoo
我就是硬汉
I'm a tough guy
那就操我
Then you fuck me
你想和妮可做 对吗？
Have a woman like Nicole you know that right
好爽
Yeah
把我想象成妮可来操吧
Fuck me like you wanted to fuck Nicole
继续操我
Go ahead
你敢吗？
Dare you
这就是令你在衣柜里想入非非的东西？
So this is what you thought about in the closet
好爽
Yeah
好棒...好舒服
Yeah yeah
天哪
Oh my god
老天...好爽
Oh my god yeah
你肉棒好舒服
You're a little fucking cock so good
好棒
Yeah
就这样吗？
Are you just gonna
让你有感觉
Let you have it
我只是让你体验一下
I think I was just gonna let you have it
跪下舔我
In their fucking knees
哦...好爽
Oh yeah
就这样别动
Stay right now
舔我的屁眼
Eat that asshole
好爽
Fuck
你到底渴求着什么？亚伦
What is it that you want Aaron
渴求着什么
What do you want
你要什么
我觉得你想得到她的全部
I think you wanting all of it
悬崖勒马
Got you into this situation in the first cliffs
你确定这是你想要的吗？
Are you sure you want all of it
不管怎样 我都完蛋了
I'm fucked either way
她的小穴如此令你着迷
That pussy is too good for you
过来操我屁眼
You should fuck my ass
哦...老天
Oh my god
老天
God
好棒
Fuck yes
哦，我的天哪
Oh my goodness
天哪...好舒服
Oh my god oh yes
求而不得的情绪令你更加易怒
Since your emotions will get you anger every time
凝视你自己
Look at you
冷静思考
Calm down think
它让你陷入泥泞 问题接踵而至
Get you into all the trouble ，doesn't it？
你渴求的只是外表光鲜艳丽
All the skin that you could ever want
好棒...爽
Yes yes yes yes
噢...好爽...让我高潮
Oh god fuck yes make me fucking come anything over
这是个错误
It's the mistake
如此渴望
It sounds so desperate
那种愉悦身心的感觉
So desperate for that fucking feeling
真棒
Yes yes
来吧...射给我
Come on give it to me
给我精液
Give it to me
这就是你所渴求的
This is what you want it this is what you want it
这就是你想要的
This is what you want it
好爽
Yes yes
老天
Oh my god
有所价值
This is feeling worthy
迷茫所失
Not that can't see it
你太舒服了
It's too good for you
你带走了它
You take that also
我接受你施舍给我的一切
I'll take anything you want to give
爽
Yes
感觉如何？
What about the way it feels
好他妈...爽
It feels so...fuck
你偷窥了很多次
You do a lot of looking
在衣柜里
From the inside of closet
你不必痴迷于这种感觉
You don't have to get this feeling, do you?
爽...好舒服
Yeah yeah
你敢吗？
How dare you？
哦...舒服
Oh yeah
我的天
Oh my god
哦...好棒...好舒服
Oh fuck yeah yeah
好爽
Yeah
你在盯着奶子吗？
So are you staring at these
感觉很舒服
They feel really good
好爽...好舒服
Yes yes
我现在要上你了
I'm gonna use you now
老天
Oh my god
好爽
Yeah
我的天啊
Oh my god
哦...天哪
你一直都这么快
You're always in such a fucking rush
更深
Deep
哦...看看你
Oh look at you
你如此渴望 和我交合
You're such a desperate and you're so fucking with me
好爽...好舒服
Yes yes
老天啊
Oh my god
太棒了
Fucking good
天哪
Oh god
好棒
Yes
好舒服
好爽...好舒服
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
好棒
Yes yes
好舒服...好爽
好爽
Yes
真爽
Fuck
你快要从桌子上滑下去了
You gonna slide yourself right off the fucking table
冷静下来吧
Maybe you should calm down
好
Okay
当你看不见时似乎无法享受这愉悦
Seems like you don't enjoy it as much when you can't watch
你他妈给我看着
Let you gonna fucking watch
你想看什么？
What do you want to see
这就是你渴求的吗
Is that what you need
好爽
Yeah
好棒
当你真正得到它时你会感到恐惧
It's because it scares you to actually get it
让你害怕了 不对吗？
Scares you to actually get it doesn't it
好他妈爽
You know what the fucking goods
我感觉好舒服 你明白吗
You know what I was looking good
好爽
Yes yes
太爽了
That's so good
修理工
Just a schedule boy
你就这点本事吗？
Is that all you've got
你觉得插进了我的小穴
You think you got it in you
并非如此
No I...
总是表现得像个硬汉
Always acting like a tough gun
你总会明白的
You finally get it
你不是它的对手
You can't really handle it
如果我是你操过的最后一个女人呢
What if this was the last piece of flesh you ever got
你知道会被我永远关起来
Cause you know I'm gonna put you away for good right?
就这样
This is it
你最后一次做爱
Your last ride
快点吧
Come on
我要感受到你的肉棒
I wanna feel you I wanna feel it
好爽
Yes
好棒
就这里...就是这里
This is it this is it
就这样...你所得到的
This is it and this is all you've got
你流汗了...你在流汗
You're sweating you're sweating
你应该发觉的
You should be
有用吗？
Does that help
给我你得到的全部
Give me everything you got give me everything
一切都毫无意义
Everything is doing nothing
坐下
Sit down
手放在背后
Hands behind your back
去吧
Do it
我希望一切都...
I hope it was all...
值得
worth
天哪
Oh god
还想我继续吗？
And you still want me to keep going yeah
你太好猜了
You're so predictable
你太容易对付了
You're so easy to pay
我想知道你脑袋里在想什么
I wonder what's going on in that little head of yours but then
我觉得我现在已经知道了
I realize I already know
真棒
Yeah
你在乎这种感觉
You care about is this feeling
昙花一现
Really that's so transient
毫无意义
So meaningless
噢...你想射出来，对吗？
Oh I can tell you wanna cum don't you yeah
你只需要让肉棒舒服就行了
You don't have to all that you don't fucking cock here you
感受一下我所做的
Wanna feel what I do is feel
这就是你要的吗
That's what you want
你想要什么
What you want
老天
God
好爽
Yes yes
你知道吗？亚伦
You know Aaron
有两种方法可以击中目标
There are two ways to land a target
一种是瞄准
One way you just shoot
再瞄准
and shoot
直到击中你的目标
Until you hit your mark
你一直在调整准心直到能成功
You keep adjusting until you get there
但最可靠的方法是
But the surest way
直接开枪
Is to shoot and shoot
不做任何调整
Without making any adjustments
随后你要做的是
Then all you have to do
走到即将开枪的地方
Just walk over to where the shots landed
把目标引到最上方
You draw your target right on top
扣动扳机
Put a bull's eye
鲜血弥漫
around the cluster
你在担心你的指纹
You're worried about your fingerprints
对...
Yes
你该离开了
You should go now
我们另一边见
See you on the other side
另一边见
谁杀了他
导演
凯登·克罗斯